No, like, you can't even have a recipe.
Go to Pioneer Woman.
I know Garland.
Like, I'm giving you, like, there's recipe.
Like, there's cookbooks.
Like, fire it out.
Fire it out.
So, I'm very interested to see what's going to look like.
Yeah, it's, it's...
I'm just, yeah, I'm just wondering from your side of things, like, how interesting it.
You just can't use it in the history field, I think.
A lot of profs are doing, like, either...
Canvas lockdown browser, but there's still ways you can cheat with it.
Yeah, I didn't even think about that.
I think a lot of it's going to be blue books and just written out, which, okay, I think that's great.
That's more what grad school looks like if you're interested in that.
And it's better learning in communication skills, writing skills, and critical thinking skills.
And those are all four missions of a lot of the history classes that you know.
That's perfect then.
Yeah, I think it's perfect.
As, um...
Can you tell?
Whenever you read it, can you tell?
Okay, I just was wondering.
Because I write how I talk.
So... Oh, that's really, like, accessible then.
Yeah.
So, like, if you use 15 commas and it's a single sentence, I just know that's how you talk.
That's great.
I'll tell you through a couple periods.
Right, right, right.
But if it's...
I use endashes, and I use all through commas.
I've had to stop using them because of it.
I'm an endash trooper.
I don't take that from me.
That's so valid.
So, again, if it's a kid that is doing a weirdly okay job, then I'll kind of like, hmm.
Again, it's sort of early in the semester.
We'll see.
I think handwriting is also a big thing.
If you have chicken scratch, then I'm going to say, you don't probably write a lot.
Yeah, yeah.
Because I write everything out a lot before I type it up.
But it's just a mindset I don't know a lot about.
But you can 100% tell.
You can 100% tell.
It's interesting to me who can and cannot tell because there's very much a generational gap to who can and cannot tell.
Especially with generative AI.
Pictures...
That's weird, but people can't tell.
It's getting so...
I've actually got tripped for the very first time, and I was like, wow, this is getting really good and very scary.
Yeah.
I think in the next five years, there'll be a whole thing, like, made by humans.
Right.
We're not using generative AI.
I do think that will be that.
Like, I think in that first episode of Vince Gilligan's new show, Blurberus, have you seen it on Apple TV?
Mm-hmm.
The end credits said, like, made 100% by humans.
Awesome.
Yeah.
So, like... That's going to be, like, the...
I think it's going to be a good thing.
Yeah.
I think the marketing campaigns...
Exactly.
I think it's going to become a sense of artisanal...
Right.
...made, handcrafted by humans.
Like, organic.
It's the new...
I 100% submit into organic.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I can see that, too.
I think you just have to shift it, market it, of, like, this is human-made, humanized.
Right.
Yeah.
Artisanal crafted, as you said.
It's going to be... Yeah.
Higher luxury.
Right.
Because real people made it.
I think that...
You're right.
That does have a lot to do with consumerism and mass production.
You tell someone the water impact of it and they think nothing of it.
You're telling Californians to take 15 minute showers and then building a data center that uses the water in a day so someone can tell them make a schedule for me today.
Yeah.
Make this email.
Make a make this like picture of me alive.
And so I think also just everyday life I don't
If someone shows me something AI, I go, ew.
I'll be rude.
Like, I don't care.
It's stopping it on the local, personal level and saying, gross.
You use AI?
I don't, like, I will be 100% mean about that.
I don't care.
Shame them.
If anything, shameful.
Yes.
So, again, is this different when it comes to math or science?
I'm sure.
But all humanity, this side of campus, we have no business.
We have no business.
None of the humanities, no.
No.
Yeah, that's why I was very, like, hackles raised when they told us to.
Yeah.
No, I completely get that.
No, it's.
Yeah.
No, but I think.
You know, people, students are always happy to be here.
You can build it on campus.
They want to be here.
They are excited.
I think that's wonderful.
So.
What are some, like, say that this whole place closed down tomorrow.
What are some of the memories that will stick with you going forward that you tell, like, your family about?
Yeah, probably my training.
Just that will take.
career shift.
I hate that with me, obviously.
But Megan and I got the giggles the other day.
There's a video of Michael Jackson.
He's promoting a tour.
And he goes, like, I hate touring.
I love touring.
And they go, like, Michael, do one, like, do positive.
And so they cut and he goes, I love to tour.
And he's like, man, I love to tour.
I don't know, you know, we just kept doing it, and I really, I'm like, for some reason, like, the song Mary Did You Know About brought up, so I was like, Mary, did you talk?
It was just so funny.
But yeah, I'd say probably most of my memories with Megan, and that's probably my biggest thing.
What I do share with family is more like my personal stripes, highs and lows, the more academic side of things, yeah.
That's really nice.
Yeah.
I love you too.
I have some legacy questions so Haskell Monroe and he he's one of the people that did like hundreds of the interviews that we have and he has a list of his questions are wild from okay
Wild.
But some of them that I think I should continue on in the legacy is this one.
If you're a consultant to A&M leadership today, what advice you would give them?
And this is a question from him from the 70s.
I'd say fire board of regents and have them be educators.
I'm not saying just, I don't need PhDs in there.
Right.
I can have high school teachers, elementary school teachers that are interested in administrative work.
As long as you have an educator background, that's who should be making decisions for this campus and the system as a whole.
I'd say stop buying out these small schools.
We don't need the system to be bigger.
I think it's attractive, obviously.
Focus on what's going on here.
Let's look at, you know, what are our food options on campus?
conjoined our food options on campus.
You can only go to like the, at the express little like gas station pretty much here.
But engineering buildings have Starbucks in the engineering buildings.
How are we showing favoritism to certain majors and colleges?
And I understand it's money and enrollment numbers.
I do, I get that.
But how do we make those other departments employees attractive?
it'll draw more people it'll draw more people in yeah you know ask yourself what do you want to be known as just an ag or just an engineering school when if you're in our own university every department's impacted in that and that is evident and we just had a Pulitzer Prize winner Caleb Daniel he went he got his master's here wild yes so um what else what was he English history history history do you guys have his information yeah he wrote that right so
or reach out to him for an interview or something.
Yes, yes, no, please.
Yeah, probably that.
In the nicest way possible.
No, yeah.
Just, I'd lean towards ags, teaching, raising ags and making decisions for ags.
Yeah, just, example, like they dissolved the Faculty Senate.
That's who could have been reviewing syllabi.
Yeah.
But you're overworking your department heads.
Mm-hmm.
So that was, yeah.
Yeah.
Um, this also is another one that he would always ask is that if you were given a million dollars and you had to give it to some part of this university, what would you invest it in?
Like what, what, what needs it, or what would you?
Hmm.
Probably library.
Probably some of the dismal animal hospital.
Hmm.
I work there for a little bit.
And they do so much.
There's an actual also vet people go to.
Oh, wow.
George Strait goes there for his animals.
Oh, cool.
It's just, it serves the community as well.
Probably a little more transportation.
Some of those buses are a little old.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd probably say that.
I think that's a good way of using it.
Yeah, I think that's a good way.
I hope, yeah.
I've heard everything from all to football to, yeah, I've heard everything from.
Yeah, they're good.
Yeah.
A million dollars to the football is like $10,000, like comparatively, like that's how much it is.
That's wild.
They're okay.
Yeah, they're good.
I promise you they're okay.
Yeah, truly.
Is there any topics that you really did want to talk about that I just didn't touch on?
Nothing?
Okay.
And then my last one is, what are the feelings that you hold in your heart for Texas A&M?
Right now?
Yeah, two weeks ago I might have changed.
Appreciation, you know, being my husband, being my education.
Frustration right now.
Defensiveness.
I'm very defensive of A&M.
There's the, you know, whenever it's UT rivalry week, it's like, who didn't get into UT goes to A&M.
I never applied to UT.
I never wanted to be in Austin.
Like, I chose here.
Yeah, just love, defensiveness, and frustration, I think, probably right now.
Yeah.
I think it's because of the love.
It's because of the love so much.
It's breaking your heart.
You know what it can be?
so and what it is because if you didn't care about it then it wouldn't yeah yeah if this really is just a place you're getting a piece of paper who cares but i have every intention to have a long relationship with am so yeah i think that's what makes this place actually special the amount of alumni who come we're such an engaged alumni truly like
rivals the nation.
Really, truly.
So I think that's so special.
So pissing off half of the alumni probably had a good decision.
It truly isn't.
Yeah.
Well, thank you.
Of course.